<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevOps on Lumy</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DevOps on Lumy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Battery-Less Sensing of Body Movements Through Differential Backscattered RFID Signals</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publications/joun1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/publications/joun1/</guid>
      <description>RFID tags not only can be used as identification devices, with antenna sensing techniques, they can also be used as low-cost and battery-less sensors. However, RFID antenna sensing relies on the impedance and/or gain modulation of the tag’s antenna, and extracts the sensing information through the RSSI variation of the backscattered signals. The sensing information is prone to the interferences and noises in the reader-tag communication channel, as well as the distance variations if the sensors are in constant motion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-Textile Battery-Less Displacement and Strain Sensor for Human Activities Tracking</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publications/joun2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/publications/joun2/</guid>
      <description>Wearable sensors demand flexible and concealable devices that can be seamlessly integrated with apparels and clothes. E-textile sensors and devices, built from specially functionalized fibers and yarns and constructed with embroidery and woven processes, provide an ideal solution for different wearable applications. In this article, we propose a textile-based, embroidered passive strain and displacement sensor functioned as a UHF RFID antenna that can be aesthetically integrated with garment fabrics. The antenna structure consists of a dipole arm and a coupling loop mounted with an RFID chip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wearable Deformation Sensor with Ambient Interference Rejection Using Differential Backscattered RFID Signals</title>
      <link>https://example.com/publications/conf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/publications/conf1/</guid>
      <description>RFID technology not only enables wireless identification, it also provides the platform for battery-less antenna sensing capabilities, i.e., the sensing information is modulated by the antenna impedance, and it can later be extracted from the backscattered signals by the readers. However, antenna sensing is prone to interference and ambient environment impacts, such as distance variation and noise in the transmission path. These factors can cause amplitude and phase changes of the received signals, and deteriorate the quality of the sensing information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patent: New anti-interference sensor based on RFID</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/patent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/patent/</guid>
      <description>TBA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Marketplace Plugins</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/marketplace/</guid>
      <description>Multiple plugins used by thousands of teams that provide enhanced functionality of Atlassian’s core products (primarily JIRA and Bamboo) to enrich CI/CD capabilities, DevOps automation, or productivity. Functionality spans user interface, web services and persistence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
